export const JsQuizData = [
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the primary purpose of JavaScript?",
      options: ["Styling web pages", "Creating interactive elements", "Database management", "Server-side scripting"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which keyword is used to declare variables in JavaScript?",
      options: ["var", "let", "const", "variable"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What does the 'NaN' stand for in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Not a Number", "Null and Negative", "Negative and Null", "Notable Number"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "In JavaScript, what is the purpose of the 'setTimeout' function?",
      options: ["Executing a function after a specified delay", "Setting a timer for the entire script", "Pausing the script execution", "Delaying the loading of external resources"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which function is used to print output in JavaScript?",
      options: ["console.log()", "print()", "display()", "output()"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'if' statement in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Looping", "Conditional execution", "Function declaration", "Variable declaration"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "How do you comment a single line in JavaScript?",
      options: ["/* comment */", "// comment", "# comment", "-- comment"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which operator is used for strict equality in JavaScript?",
      options: ["==", "===", "=", "!=="],
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'while' loop in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Iterating over properties of an object", "Executing a block of code repeatedly while a condition is true", "Creating a function", "Defining a class"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'this' keyword in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Referring to the current object", "Creating a new variable", "Declaring a function", "Accessing the prototype object"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which function is used to convert a string to an integer in JavaScript?",
      options: ["toInt()", "parseInt()", "stringToNumber()", "castInt()"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'addEventListener' method in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Adding a style to an element", "Attaching an event handler to an element", "Creating a new element", "Removing an element from the DOM"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which statement is used to terminate the execution of a loop in JavaScript?",
      options: ["break", "exit", "return", "terminate"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the result of the expression '5' - 3 in JavaScript?",
      options: ["2", "8", "53", "NaN"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which object is a collection of key-value pairs in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Array", "List", "Object", "Set"],
      answer: 3
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What does the 'typeof' operator return in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Type of the variable", "Size of the variable", "Value of the variable", "Index of the variable"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which method is used to remove the last element from an array in JavaScript?",
      options: ["pop()", "removeLast()", "deleteLast()", "splice()"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'try...catch' statement in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Defining a function", "Handling errors", "Creating a loop", "Conditionally executing code"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "Which function is used to round a number to the nearest integer in JavaScript?",
      options: ["round()", "ceil()", "floor()", "truncate()"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      title: "JavaScript",
      question: "What is the purpose of the 'map' method in JavaScript?",
      options: ["Creating a new array with the results of a provided function", "Removing elements from an array", "Sorting an array", "Concatenating arrays"],
      answer: 1
    }
]